<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>content on Poojalaya : Pandit Viswanathan Gurukkal</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/content/</link>
    <description>Recent content in content on Poojalaya : Pandit Viswanathan Gurukkal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Untitled. All rights reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Panditji</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about-panditji/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about-panditji/</guid>
      <description>Pandit Viswanathan Gurukkal is from Erode. He first served Sri Meenakshi Sundareswarar Temple in Kaspa Pasur, Erode Tamil Nadu.
Guru: BrahmaShri K.L.V. Ramana Dixitar &amp;amp; Dr. K. Pitchai Sivachariar
Education: Sri Raja Vedha Kavya Patasala, Kumbakonam, Tamil Nadu, India (Established in 1542 A.D)
Higher Education: Sri Karpaga Vinayagar Vedhagama Vidhyalayam, Pillayarpatti, Tamil Nadu, India
Specialization Vedha Vichakshana, Hindu Religious Course, Krishna Yajur Vedam and Shivaagamam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aayushya Homam</title>
      <link>https://example.org/homams/aayushya-homam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/homams/aayushya-homam/</guid>
      <description>Ayur Devatha Ayur Devatha also called as the Jagan Matha safeguards every living creature in the earth.
 Om Haam Ayur Devathaabhyo Namaha
 Dhanvantri is the God of Medicine and Ayur Veda, he is an avatar of Sri Vishnu. He holds Amruta the divine nectar of immortality. He also is the creator of sacred herbs and plants, that are used as medicine. He is called as The Divine Doctor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homam &amp; Havan</title>
      <link>https://example.org/homam-havan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/homam-havan/</guid>
      <description>Agni, the Holy Fire: Agni, The fire God, plays a pivotal role while performing the Havan. Agni is considered the mouth of the Gods and Goddesses and, the medium that conveys offerings to them in a Havan. Agni is part of many Hindu rites-of-passage ceremonies such as celebrating a birth (lighting a lamp), prayers (aarti lamp), at weddings (the yajna where the bride and groom circle the fire seven times) and at death (cremation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homam &amp; Havan</title>
      <link>https://example.org/homams/homam-havan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/homams/homam-havan/</guid>
      <description>Agni, the Holy Fire: Agni, The fire God, plays a pivotal role while performing the Havan. Agni is considered the mouth of the Gods and Goddesses and, the medium that conveys offerings to them in a Havan. Agni is part of many Hindu rites-of-passage ceremonies such as celebrating a birth (lighting a lamp), prayers (aarti lamp), at weddings (the yajna where the bride and groom circle the fire seven times) and at death (cremation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homam &amp; Havan</title>
      <link>https://example.org/homams/homam-havan1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/homams/homam-havan1/</guid>
      <description>Level2 Agni, the Holy Fire: Agni, The fire God, plays a pivotal role while performing the Havan. Agni is considered the mouth of the Gods and Goddesses and, the medium that conveys offerings to them in a Havan. Agni is part of many Hindu rites-of-passage ceremonies such as celebrating a birth (lighting a lamp), prayers (aarti lamp), at weddings (the yajna where the bride and groom circle the fire seven times) and at death (cremation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Ganapati Homam</title>
      <link>https://example.org/homams/sri-ganapati-homam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/homams/sri-ganapati-homam/</guid>
      <description>Sri Ganapati Sri Ganapati the elephant faced God, is the Adi Baghavan, meaning first of all the Gods. He is the Vignaharta, the God who removes obstacles, that impede our progress in life. Sri Ganapati is also known as the father of all arts and sciences.
Sri Ganapati Homam   It is ideal to perform the Sri Ganapati Homam on the Sankata Hara Chaturthi day, the 4th day of Krishna Paksha (Dark Lunar Phase), every month of Lunar Hindu Calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>